SHRIKANT ADSULE

shrikantadsule59@gmail.com

9987677681

Mumbai, India 400089

SKILLS

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- ASP.NET
- MVC
- C#
- .NET CORE
- Restful, MVC
- · Web services
- Win forms
- WCF

Web Technologies:

- HTML
- CSS
- JAVASCRIPTS Database:
- SOL Server
- ORACLE
- MySQL Versioning:
- Azure Devops,GIT
- TFS,SVN

EDUCATION

Karmaveer Bhaurao Patil College Vashi

Vashi, Navi Mumbai • 04/2019

Bachelor of Science: Information Technology

CERTIFICATIONS

C and C++ certification from Anubhav institute chembur.

Data base Management System DBMS certification in college.

.Net Mvc Internship in the academic year.

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Software Developer with 4+ years of experience and the ability to handle more than one project at a time. And ensuring timely delivery of the tasks assigned with minimum rework. Maintaining documents and, reports and updating them. In constant communication with the clients and providing them with the optimal solution

Organized and dependable candidate successful at managing multiple priorities with a positive attitude. Willingness to take on added responsibilities to meet team goals.

& Shrikant Adsule | LinkedIn

WORK HISTORY

Path InfoTech Limited - Senior Programmer Malad Mumbai, MH • 07/2024 - Current

 As a Full Stack Developer, I specialize in ASP.NET, ASP.NET MVC, SQL Server, and Oracle, managing both frontend and backend development. I oversee multiple projects simultaneously, handling development, deployment following the SDLC Cycle and system optimization.

IDBI Intech Limited - Senior Software Developer CBD Belapur, Navi Mumbai, MH • 08/2022 - 07/2024

- Responsible for developing and maintaining application that is currently in use for bank by taking care of sensitive Data.
- Centralizing system that had multiple API projects into single MVC-based application saved time for coded configurations
- Resulting in better maintenance and completing developments on time, deployments in and production are also done
- Work with multiple projects of internal bank technology using MVC ASP.NET API, and constant communication with LIC client for client application, providing them with optimal solution.
- Saved time and resources by identifying and fixing bugs before product deployment managed over 5 plus applications.
- Increased application security by conducting vulnerability assessments and implementing appropriate countermeasures.

Hinduja Global Solutions - Junior Software Developer Khar Road, Mumbai, MH • 01/2021 - 07/2022

- In charge of handling 2 projects at same time, with C# Windows Forms and API technology and SQL server.
- Designed reusable and reliable code for use within distributed cloud environments Updated old code bases to modern development standards, improving functionality
- Tuned systems to boost performance

Thyrocare Technologies Limited - Executive Software Developer

Juinagar, Navi Mumbai, MH • 12/2019 - 06/2020

- Delivered project reports and milestone updates to supervisor Handle ASP.NET application and reports and resolved ASP.NET MVC Applications issues
- Tested and deployed scalable and complex software's products.